Guide to the United Nations Food and Agriculture Organization home economics publications, 1960-1988.
United Nations Food and Agriculture Organization home economics publications
- Report of the Third Session of the Working Party on Home Economics for Europe, 1972; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 28 pp (Box 2)
- Report to the Government of Uganda: Feasibility Study on Requirements and Demands for Graduates in Home Economics for Rural Development, 1970; Janelid, Ingrid; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 34 pp (Box 2)
- Report on the Meeting on Long-Term Planning in Home Economics in Europe, 1964; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 41 pp (Box 2)
  Meeting: Rome, Italy; November 3rd to 13th, 1964
- Rural Development and Education: A Family Ecosystem Approach, 1977-06; Axinn, Nancy W.; 10 pp (Box 2)
- Al-Raida: Institute for Women's Studies in the Arab World, 1980-08-01; Al-Raida; 16 pp (Box 2)
  Vol. III, No. 13
- La Capacitacíon de Economistas del Hogar para el Desarollo Rural, 1980; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 159 pp (Box 2)
- Manual of Supervised Agricultural Credit in Latin America, 1955-11; Brossard, Dario B.; Institute of Inter-American Affairs; Foreign Operations Administration of the United States of America; American International Association; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United States; 63 pp (Box 2)
- Population Education Seminar for Egerton College Staff, 1973; The Government of Kenya; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 130 pp (Box 2)
  Meeting: Njoro, Kenya; May 16th to 18th, 1973
- Estudio Sobre la Intervencion de la Mujer en la Comercializacion de Productos Agropecuarios y Alimentos en el Litoral Ecuatoriano, 1979; Segura, Nancy Torre; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 110 pp (Box 2)
- Training Home Economists for Rural Development, 1978; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 125 pp (Box 2)
- Home Management and Consumer Education in Rural Development Programmes: Latin America, 1972; Cásseres, Virginia Lattes de; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 84 pp (Box 2)
- Child Care: A Handbook for Village Workers and Leaders, 1967; Keister, Mary Elizabeth; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 65 pp (Box 2)
- Women in the Urban Labor Markets of Africa: The Case of Tanzania, 1980-04; Shields, Nwanganga; World Bank; 142 pp (Box 2)
- FAO/ECA/SIDA Seminar on Home Economics Development Planning for English-Speaking Countries in Africa, 1972; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 176 pp (Box 2)
  Gift of Ludmilla Marin-Jenkins; Meeting: Addis Ababa, Ethiopia; March 6th to 23rd, 1972
- Workshop on Food Preservation and Storage, 1976; Government of the United Republic of Tanzania; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 107 pp (Box 2)
  Meeting: Kibaha, Tanzania; July 21st to August 8th, 1975
- Problemas Economicos y Sociales de Los Andes: Venezolanos (Parte I y II), Undated; El Consejo de Bienestar Rural; 366 pp (Box 2)
- Preparation of Baseline Studies on Women in Rural Households, 1981; Home Economics and Social Programmes Services; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 33 pp (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Integration of Rural Women in National Development in Indonesia, 1977-11; Sajogyo, Pudjiwati; Home Economics and Social Programmes Services; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 91 pp (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Resolutions and Decision Adopted by the World Conference of International Women's Year 1975, 1975; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 35 pp (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Women's Role in Root and Tuber Crops Production, 1983; Martin, Franklin W.; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 17 pp (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Meeting: Rome, Italy; December 7th to 14th, 1983
- Rice Farming Systems: Case Studies of Current Developments and Future Alternatives in Mangrove Swamp Rice and Irrigated Rice, 1983; Dey, Jennie; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 23 pp (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Women's Role in Horticultural Production in Developing Countries, 1983; Accati, Elena Garibaldi; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 19 pp (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Role of Women in Rural Development, 1975; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 23 pp (Box 2, Folder 2)
- The Socio-Economic Role of Farm Women in Agricultural and National Development in West Africa, 1971; Janelid, Ingrid; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 10 pp (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Meeting: Zaria, Nigeria; December 13th to 18th, 1971
- Training Women for Development: A Joint Enterprise in Africa, 1977; Ritchie, Jean A. S.; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 8 pp (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Guidelines for the Integration of Women in Rural Development, 1980-05; Ad-Hoc Sub-Group on Women in Rural Development; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 28 pp (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Evaluacion de Programas de Accion y de Educacion de la Mujer Rural, 1981; Jiménez, Mónica; Aylwin, Nidia; Gissi, Jorge; Jiménez, Marcela; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 80 pp (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Findings from Socio-Economic Surveys in Madang Province, 1977; Hard af Segerstad, M.; 9 pp (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Integrated Programme for Better Family Living, 1972; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 47 pp (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Meeting: Kampala, Uganda; July 14th to 20th, 1972
- Summary of the Development of the Home Economics Program in the Extension Service in Spain, Undated; Ortiz, Virginia G.; Spanish Extension Service; 23 pp (Box 2, Folder 3)
- A Selected Bibliography on Food Habits (Socio-Economic Aspects of Food and Nutrition), 1974-09; Den Hartog, A. P.; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 89 pp (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Report on the Home Economics Aspects of the UN Special Fund Project "Integrated Agricultural Programme for Education, Research and Extension Work, Chapingo, Mexico", 1971; Diño, Paz; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 12 pp (Box 2, Folder 3)
- The Agricultural Division of Labor by Sex: Myths, Facts and Contradictions in the Northern Peruvian Sierra, 1977; Deere, Carmen Diana; Joint National Meeting of the Latin American Studies Association and the African Studies Association; 29 pp (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Meeting: Houston, Texas; November 2nd to 5th, 1977
- Programs to Improve the Position of Women in a Traditional Culture: An Evaluation of a Rural Women's Development Center in Libya, 1978; Allaghi, Farida; 13 pp (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Meeting: Uppsala, Sweden; August 14th to 19th, 1978
- "We Have Planned-O": A 20-Minute Playlet on Planning for Better Family Living, 1972; Graves, Patsy; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 8 pp (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Report on Planning for Better Family Living Programme: A Project Working Paper, 1973; Segarra-Ortiz, Hilda; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 57 pp (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Report of the Programme for Better Family Living Activies in Tanzania, October 1972 to March 1973, 1973; Junod, Violaine Idelette; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 59 pp (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Report on Programmes for Better Family Living, Kenya, 1973-1974, 1974; Bustrillos, Nena R.; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 23 pp (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Report on Programmes for Better Family Living, Kenya, 1974; Barghouti, Shawki M.; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 15 pp (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Assessment of the World Food Situation, Present and Future, 1974; United Nations World Food Conference; 128 pp (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Meeting: Rome, Italy; November 5th to 16th, 1974
- Summary of United Nations and FAO World Conference Resolutions and Recommendations Concerning Women in Rural Development (1970 - 1979), 1979-10; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 17 pp (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Report on the FAO/SIDA/DSE Inter-Regional Symposium on Integrated Rural Development, 1978; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 133 pp (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Meeting: Berlin, Federal Repulic of Germany; September 19th to 23rd, 1977
- Social Impact Analysis: A Model and Strategy for Implementation in Development Assistance, 1981; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 23 pp (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Adequacy of the Indicators and Pilot Studies for Low Income and Other Disadvantaged Groups, 1982; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 36 pp (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Meeting: Addis Ababa, Ethiopia; May 10th to 15th, 1982
- Learning About Rural Women, 1979-12; Zeidenstein, Sondra; Studies in Family Planning; 118 pp (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Vol. 10, No. 11/12
- Women in Development, 1977-05; Wingspread Workshop; The Johnson Foundation; 40 pp (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Meeting: Wellesley College, Massachusetts; June 1976
- Food Deficits and Agricultural Policies in Sub-Saharan Africa, 1984-09; Lofchie, Michael F.; Commins, Stephen K.; The Hunger Project; 36 pp (Box 2, Folder 9)
  No. 2
- Bread and Stones: The Salvage of the Philae Monuments, Undated; World Food Programme in Egypt; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 20 pp (Box 2, Folder 9)
- You Can Do Something about Rural Development, 1976-04-28; World Young Women's Christian Association; 42 pp (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Seven inserts
- [Untitled], 1977-11; Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations; 51 pp (Box 2, Folder 9)